<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LaundryHub</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="service">24 Hour Service</string>
    <string name="expresslaundry">Express Laundry</string>
    <string name="homedelivery">Home Delivery</string>
    <string name="rewards">Rewards</string>
    <string name="service1">Go to our laundry app or website and schedule your wash as per your convenience. We will take it from there. Hassel free, fast and simple!</string>
    <string name="discover_text">We offers you 24 hour laundry service and we take dirt very seriously.Our experts with the help of our state of art machinery ensure that your clothes come back looking clean and fresh every time.</string>
    <string name="shop_text">We take dirt very seriously. Our experts, with the help of our state of art machinery ensure that your clothes come back looking clean, tidier and fresh every time</string>
    <string name="offers_text">Find great offers while you discover</string>
    <string name="rewards_text">Select your current location for ordering purpose and pick convenient time and our driver will be on the way Dont worry we will bring the bag</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="terms">Please read the following terms and conditions carefully.</string>

    <string name="termsdescription">Customers use of any of Company services indicates an agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions set forth below.Items which are given to the company for cleaning/repairing will termed as article in this agreement.This agreement is strictly beteween company and customer and does not in any way constitute or imply any relationship with any other parties.</string>
    <string name="note1">1. Company will use reasonable efforts to try to ensure that washing,drying and folding services are maintained at a high level of quality.</string>
    <string name="note2">2. Customers are requested to examine the articles at the time of delivery; we would not be held responsible for any damages that are found after delivery of processed articles.</string>
    <string name="note3">3. Urgent delivery of articles would be charged 50% extra over the regular tariff.</string>
    <string name="note4">5. If not satisfied with the quality of any service offered,customers should get in touch with the company within 24 hours for resolution.</string>
    <string name="note5">4. We are not responible for fastness, colour bleeed, colour running, shrinkage, damages to establishments or embroidery work on the articles during processing.</string>
    <string name="note6">6. Company reserves the right to refuse cleaning any garment.</string>
    <string name="note7">7. Company accepts no liability for special care and delicate items that require special attention to be cleaned.</string>
    <string name="note8">8. For a better experience,while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information,including your current location,Internet and Network state.</string>


    <string name="place_order">1. Go to our laundry app and schedule your wash as per your convenience. We will take it from there. Hassel free, fast and simple!</string>
    <string name="pick_up">2. Just be ready with your Laundry, we will be right there with our eco-friendly laundry cart. We will grab away all the dirty clothes from your home.</string>
    <string name="washandiron">3. We take dirt very seriously. Our experts, with the help of our state of art machinery ensure that your clothes come back looking clean, tidier and fresh every time.</string>
    <string name="delivery">4. Your clothes will be delivered at your doorstep on time and as fresh as daisy. Now getting your laundry done is that convenient.</string>
    //Bottom Navigation menu's
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="mycart">My Cart</string>
    <string name="cart">Cart</string>
    <string name="Help">Help</string>
    <string name="payment">Payment</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="logout_message">Are you sure want to Logout ?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>


    <string name="no_internet_message">No Internet Connection</string>

    <string name="service_details">Our dry cleaning services offer the same pick up and delivery as our laundry services. You can even give us your laundry and dry cleaning at the same time, just make sure they are separated.</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mylocation">Map</string>

    <string name="map_key" translatable="false">AIzaSyCF6L9NRuvk2VzZFF9ACwSD2vqJxaNKO3g</string>

</resources>